Guide to the Clark E. Warburton papers, 1920-1979
George Mason University Libraries
- Clark Warburton Papers
  - Miscellaneous Articles and Memoranda by Clark Warburton 1930-57 (2) (Folder 6, Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous Articles and Memoranda by Clark Warburton 1934-1951 (1) (Folder 7, Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous Articles and Memoranda by Clark Warburton 1934-51 (2) (Folder 8, Box 6)
  - The Social Organism (Folder 9, Box 6)
  - Influence of Custom in Evolution of Anglo-American Economic Society (Folder 10, Box 6)
  - Comments on the Equation of Exchange (Folder 11, Box 6)
  - Prohibition and Economic Welfare (Folder 12, Box 6)
  - Principles of Literary Criticism (Folder 13, Box 6)
  - Verses (Folder 14, Box 6)
  - Short Stories (Folder 15, Box 6)
  - Debate- Strength Of the Navy, April 1914 (Folder 16, Box 6)
  - Commencement 1914 (Folder 17, Box 6)
  - India- Our Economic Organization (Folder 18, Box 6)
  - India- A Plea for Liberal Education (Folder 19, Box 6)
  - Part Five- Three Estimates (Folder 20, Box 6)
  - Accounting Methodology- Part Two (Folder 21, Box 6)
  - January 1922 (Folder 22, Box 6)
  - What determines the rate of foreign exchange? (Folder 23, Box 6)
  - March 1922 (Folder 24, Box 6)
  - Articles Published in the Punjab Education Journal 1922-23 (Folder 25, Box 6)
  - October 1923 (Folder 26, Box 6)
  - January 1924 (1) (Folder 27, Box 6)
  - January 1924 (2) (Folder 28, Box 6)
  - July 1924 (Folder 29, Box 6)
  - October 1924 (Folder 30, Box 6)
  - February 1928- Houston Gargoyle (Folder 31, Box 6)
  - Economic Terminology- March 1928 (Folder 32, Box 6)
  - March 1928- Houston Gargoyle (Folder 33, Box 6)
  - April 1928- Houston Gargoyle (Folder 34, Box 6)
  - April 10, 1928- Houston Gargoyle (Folder 35, Box 6)
  - May 1, 1928- Houston Gargoyle (Folder 36, Box 6)
  - May 22, 1928- Houston Gargoyle (Folder 37, Box 6)
  - May 29, 1928- Houston gargoyle (Folder 38, Box 6)
  - Business Fluctuations and South's Industrial Structure, November 1930 (Folder 39, Box 6)
  - Calender Reform and Economic Investigations, August 1931 (Folder 40, Box 6)
  - December 1934 (1) (Folder 41, Box 6)
  - December 1934 (2) (Folder 42, Box 6)
  - February 1935 (Folder 43, Box 6)
  - February 1936 (Folder 44, Box 6)
  - April 1943 (Folder 45, Box 6)
  - June 1943 (Folder 46, Box 6)
  - January 1944 (Folder 47, Box 6)
  - June 1944 (Folder 48, Box 6)
  - January 1945 (Folder 49, Box 6)
  - April 1945 (Folder 50, Box 6)
  - May 1945 (1) (Folder 51, Box 6)
  - May 1945 (2) (Folder 52, Box 6)
  - June 1945 (1) (Folder 53, Box 6)
  - June 1945 (2) (Folder 54, Box 6)
  - September 1945 (Folder 55, Box 6)
  - October 1946 (1) (Folder 56, Box 6)
  - October 1946 (2) (Folder 57, Box 6)
  - October 1946 (3) (Folder 58, Box 6)
  - October 1946 (Folder 59, Box 6)
  - October 1946 (2) (Folder 60, Box 6)
  - June 1947 (1) (Folder 61, Box 6)
  - June 1947 (2) (Folder 62, Box 6)
  - May 1948 (Folder 63, Box 6)
  - November 1948 (Folder 64, Box 6)
  - December 1948 (1) (Folder 65, Box 6)
  - December 1948 (2) (Folder 66, Box 6)
  - February 1949 (Folder 67, Box 6)
  - April 1949 (Folder 68, Box 6)
  - July 1949 (Folder 69, Box 6)
  - September 1949 (Folder 70, Box 6)
  - March 1950 (Folder 1, Box 7)
  - June 1950 (Folder 2, Box 7)
  - July 1950 (Folder 3, Box 7)
  - August 1950 (Folder 4, Box 7)
  - October 1950 (Folder 5, Box 7)
  - November 1950 (Folder 6, Box 7)
  - September 1951 (1) (Folder 7, Box 7)
  - September 1951 (2) (Folder 8, Box 7)
  - February 1952 (Folder 9, Box 7)
  - March 1952 (Folder 10, Box 7)
  - April 1952 (Folder 11, Box 7)
  - December 1952 (Folder 12, Box 7)
  - March 1953 (Folder 13, Box 7)
  - June 1953 (Folder 14, Box 7)
  - Reviews of Copeland's Study of Moneyflows and Correspondence (Folder 15, Box 7)
  - December 1953 (Folder 16, Box 7)
  - December 1954 (1) (Folder 17, Box 7)
  - December 1954 (2) (Folder 18, Box 7)
  - November 1957 (Folder 19, Box 7)
  - September 1958 (Folder 20, Box 7)
  - Adequacy of the Statistical Foundation for Monetary Policy Formation- American Statistical Association, December 28, 1958. (Folder 21, Box 7)
  - 1958 (1) (Folder 22, Box 7)
  - 1958 (2) (Folder 23, Box 7)
  - November 1941 (Folder 24, Box 7)
  - December 1941 (Folder 25, Box 7)
  - April 1962 (Folder 26, Box 7)
  - February 1963 (Folder 27, Box 7)
  - February 1964 (Folder 28, Box 7)
  - April 1965 (Folder 29, Box 7)
  - June 1971 (Folder 30, Box 7)
  - Warburton, Clark- How to Stop Inflation and Reduce Interest Rates, September 1974. (Folder 31, Box 7)
  - September 1975 (Folder 32, Box 7)
  - October 1975 (Folder 33, Box 7)
  - Warburton, Clark- Federal Reserve Reform Act of 1977 (Background and Potentiality), November 1978. (Folder 34, Box 7)
  - August 1960- Hearing before subcommittee no.3. House of representatives.Monetary control under the Federal Reserve Act. (Folder 35, Box 7)
  - August 25, 1960- Committee on banking and currency.Hearing on HR 8427 p.301. Monetary control under the Federal reserve Act. (Folder 36, Box 7)
  - March 9, 1964- Statement given the subcommittee on domestic finance of the Banking and Currency Committee of the House of Representatives. Federal Reserve operations and business fluctuations. (Folder 37, Box 7)
  - March 1968, Testimony- Reply to questions regarding H.R.11. (Folder 38, Box 7)
  - April 1975, Testimony- Suggestions for Monetary Management during 1975-76 (Folder 39, Box 7)
  - Book Reviews (Folder 40, Box 7)
  - Recent Banking Legislation- talk before the Financial Group, Special Libraries Association, 5-24-39. (Folder 41, Box 7)
  - Post-War Domestic Monetary Problems- Remarks at American Economic Associations, January 23, 1944 (Washington D.C.) (Folder 42, Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous brief talks- Department of Agriculture 1945.Department of Commerce 1946.Conference on Fiscal Policy, 1941.Conference on Research in Income and Wealth, 1945. (Folder 43, Box 7)
  - Deposits- Talk at Supervisors Conference, 1947. (Folder 44, Box 7)
  - February 27, 1953- Remarks at a meeting of the Committee on Economic Policy, Chamber of Commerce of the United States. (Folder 45, Box 7)
  - Monetary Policy and Business Depressions in the U.S.- used at School of Business Seminar, Colombia University, 4-15-53. (Folder 46, Box 7)
  - May 21, 1953- Remarks at the 37th Annual Meeting National Industrial Conference Board ( How effective can monetary management be?). (Folder 47, Box 7)
  - Comments at session on "Business Cycle Analysis" - Southern Economic Association, November 13, 1953. (Folder 48, Box 7)
  - Talk at Amherst College, October 24, 1955. (Folder 49, Box 7)
  - Financial Intermediaries in National Income Accounting Paper at 1955 Conference on Research and Wealth (Studies Vol.22) (Folder 50, Box 7)
  - Role of Money in Performance of the Economy.Notes- Merrill Center for Economics, July 1956. (Folder 51, Box 7)
  - Financial Intermediaries in National Income Accounting- Meeting of National Accounts Review Committee, December 1956. (Folder 52, Box 7)
  - Pre-Keynesian Monetary Theories of Output- Talk at University of MD. Seminar, May 9, 1957. (Folder 53, Box 7)
  - Comments in Forecasting Interest rates- The Econometrics Institution, October 11, 1957. (Folder 54, Box 7)
  - Monetary Disturbances and Business Fluctuations in Two Centuries of American History-Lecture, October 1960. (Folder 55, Box 7)
  - Talk at National Economists Club, November 1968. (Folder 56, Box 7)
  - Comments on paper by Tavlas and Aschheim, "On Monetarism and Ideology"- Presented at Atlantic Economic Conference, October 1977. (Folder 57, Box 7)
  - New responsibilities for the Federal Reserve under the Federal Reserve Reform Act of 1977- Talk at National Economists Club, April 18, 1978. (Folder 58, Box 7)
  - A Sketch of Monetary Disequilibrium Theory (Monetarism) From Hume to Keynes- Talk at the University of Virginia, November 17, 1978. (Folder 59, Box 7)
  - Disequilibrium in the 1970s- Remarks made at the History of Economics Society, May 1979. (Folder 60, Box 7)
  - Correspondence 1935 (Folder 1, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1936 (Folder 2, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1937 (Folder 3, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1938 (Folder 4, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1939 (1) (Folder 5, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1939 (2) (Folder 6, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1940 (Folder 7, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1941 (Folder 8, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1942 (Folder 9, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1943 (1) (Folder 10, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1943 (2) (Folder 11, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1944 (Folder 12, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1945 (Folder 13, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1946 (Folder 14, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1947 (1) (Folder 15, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1947 (2) (Folder 16, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1947 (3) (Folder 17, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1948 (1) (Folder 18, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1948 (2) (Folder 19, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1948 (3) (Folder 20, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1948 (4) (Folder 21, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1949 (Folder 22, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1950 (Folder 23, Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1951 (Folder 1, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1952 (Folder 2, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1954 (Folder 3, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1955 (Folder 4, Box 9)
  - Norton Debits Study Correspondence 1955 (Folder 5, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1956 (Folder 6, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1957 (Folder 7, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1958 (Folder 8, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1959 (Folder 9, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1960 (Folder 10, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1961 (Folder 11A, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1962 (Folder 11B, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1963 (Folder 12, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1964 (Folder 13, Box 9)
  - Correspondence 1965 (Folder 14, Box 9)
  - Partial Lists of Memoranda (Folder 15, Box 9)
  - Memoranda 1934-35 (10) (Folder 16, Box 9)
  - Memoranda 1934-35 (2) (Folder 17, Box 9)
  - Memoranda 1936 (1) (Folder 18, Box 9)
  - Memoranda 1936 (2) (Folder 19, Box 9)
  - Memoranda June-December 1936 (3) (Folder 20, Box 9)
  - Memoranda 1937-38 (1) (Folder 21, Box 9)
  - Memoranda 1937-38 (2) (Folder 22, Box 9)
  - Memoranda 1939 (1) (Folder 23, Box 9)
  - Memoranda 1939 (2) (Folder 24, Box 9)
  - 1940 (1) (Folder 1, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1940 (20) (Folder 2, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1941 (1) (Folder 3, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1941 (2) (Folder 4, Box 10)
  - 1942 (1) (Folder 5, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1942 (2) (Folder 6, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1943 (Folder 7, Box 10)
  - 1944 (1) (Folder 8, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1944 (2) (Folder 9, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1945 (1) (Folder 10, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1945 (2) (Folder 11, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1946 (Folder 12, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1947 (Folder 13, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1948 (1) (Folder 14, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1948 (2) (Folder 15, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1949 (1) (Folder 16, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1949 (2) (Folder 17, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1949 (3) (Folder 18, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1950 (1) (Folder 19, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1950 (2) (Folder 20, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1950 (3) (Folder 21, Box 10)
  - Memoranda 1951 (Folder 1, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1952 (1) (Folder 2, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1952 (2) (Folder 3, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1953 (1) (Folder 4, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1953 (2) (Folder 5, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1954 (1) (Folder 6, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1954 (2) (Folder 7, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1955 (Folder 8, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1956 (Folder 9, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1957 (1) (Folder 10, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1957 (2) (Folder 11, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1958-61 (1) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda 1958-61 (2) (Folder 13, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1962 (1) (Folder 14, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1962 (2) (Folder 15, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1962 (3) (Folder 16, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1963 (Folder 17, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1964 (1) (Folder 18, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1964 (2) (Folder 19, Box 11)
  - Memoranda 1965 (Folder 20, Box 11)
  - Personal Banking and Business Section Civil Service (1) (Folder 21, Box 11)
  - Personal Banking and Business Section Civil Service (2) (Folder 22, Box 11)
  - Report 2/4/66 Files of the Banking and Business Section as of the end of 1965. (Folder 23, Box 11)
  - FDIC Memos on Bank Supervisory Authority- Prepared for Press and Committee on Financial Institutions. (Folder 24, Box 11)
  - Memos at FDIC- Purpose of deposit insurance. Purpose of insurance o accounts in savings institutions.Some considerations bearing on increased deposit insurance coverage. (Folder 25, Box 11)
  - Memos from FDIC:insurance coverage, banks in financial difficulties. (Folder 26, Box 11)
  - Work Reports 1935 (Folder 1, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1936 (Folder 2, Box 12)
  - Reports of Work 1937 (WPA) (Folder 3, Box 12)
  - Reports of Work 1938 (Folder 4, Box 12)
  - Reports of Work 1939 (Folder 5, Box 12)
  - Reports of Work 1940 (Folder 6, Box 12)
  - Reports of Work 1941 (Folder 7, Box 12)
  - Reports of Work 1942-42 (Folder 8, Box 12)
  - Reports of Work 1944-45 (Folder 9, Box 12)
  - Reports of Work 1946-47 (Folder 10, Box 12)
  - Reports of Work 1948-49 (1) (Folder 11, Box 12)
  - Reports of Work 1948-49 (2) (Folder 12, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1950-51 (1) (Folder 13, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1950-51 (2) (Folder 14, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1952-52 (1) (Folder 15, Box 12)
  - Work reports 1952-53 (2) (Folder 16, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1954-55 (1) (Folder 17, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1954-55 (2) (Folder 18, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1956-57-58 (1) (Folder 19, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1956-57-58 (2) (Folder 20, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1959-60 (1) (Folder 21, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1959-60 (2) (Folder 22, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1961-62 (1) (Folder 23, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1961-62 (2) (Folder 24, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1963-64 (1) (Folder 25, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1963-64 (2) (Folder 26, Box 12)
  - Work Reports 1965 (Folder 27, Box 12)
  - FDIC Reports to Insured Banks 1933-43 (Folder 28, Box 12)
  - FDIC Reports to Insured Banks 1944-55 (Folder 29, Box 12)
  - Report to Insured Banks 1956 (Folder 30, Box 12)
  - Allocation of the National Product - Report for Brookings (Folder 1, Box 13)
  - Charts- Generalized patterns of utilization of family income. Ch XII. (Folder 2, Box 13)
  - Charts- Spendable funds and their disbursement (First approximation). (Folder 3, Box 13)
  - Disbursement of Income in the U.S.- Prepared for Institute of Economics (1) (Folder 4, Box 13)
  - Disbursement of Income in the U.S.(Rough draft)- Prepared for Institute of Economics (2) (Folder 5, Box 13)
  - Preliminary Reports Submitted in April 1935- Disbursement of Income in the U.S. (Folder 6, Box 13)
  - (Folder 7, Box 13)
  - Project for Studies of end Products Submitted in 1937 to Sloan Foundation. (Folder 8, Box 13)
  - Project for search relating to end products, submitted in 1934 to Social Science Research Council, National Bureau of Economic Research, and Rockefeller Foundation. (Folder 9, Box 13)
  - Proposed research in field of business fluctuations and flow of purchasing power. (Folder 10, Box 13)
  - Social Service Research Council, January 1955. (Folder 11, Box 13)
  - Studies of national output and productive capacity submitted in 1939 to: National Industrial Conference Board and National Resources Planning Board. (Folder 12, Box 13)
  - Summaries- All governments revenues and expenditures. (Folder 13, Box 13)
  - Memos from Brookings (Folder 14, Box 13)
  - Use of national income and miscellaneous comments on incomes estimates. (Folder 15, Box 13)
  - Banking, Class use- Emory University (Notes and Outlines-Money and Banking) (Folder 1, Box 14)
  - Banking(Notes and Outlines- Money and Banking) (Folder 2, Box 14)
  - Business Finance (Lecture Notes, Emory University 1929-30) (Folder 3, Box 14)
  - Economics 200 and 400 (Rice Institute 1925-26 Grades) (Folder 4, Box 14)
  - Econ 101 B ( lecture Notes, Emory University, Fall 1929) (Folder 5, Box 14)
  - Econ 101 (Lecture Notes, Emory University, 1930-31) (Folder 6, Box 14)
  - Econ 203 Value and Distribution (Lecture Notes, Emory University, 1929-30) (Folder 7, Box 14)
  - Economics and Speculation (Lecture Notes, Emory University, 1924-30) (Folder 8, Box 14)
  - Econ 101 (Emory University Lecture Notes) (Folder 9, Box 14)
  - Econ 101 Introductory (Emory University Lecture Notes) (Folder 10, Box 14)
  - Econ 214 Industries of the U.S. (Lecture Notes, Emory University 1929-30) (Folder 11, Box 14)
  - Engineering Economies Outline- Elementary Economics, Colombia University. (Folder 12, Box 14)
  - Economics for Engineers- Special Problems, etc. (Folder 13, Box 14)
  - Elementary Economics, Lectures 39-65- Business Cycle, Markets, International Trade, Money, Price, Credit, Public Finance. (Folder 14, Box 14)
  - Elementary Economics, Lectures 81-89- Our Economic System (Lecture Notes, Rice Institute) (Folder 15, Box 14)
  - Elementary Economics, Lectures 66-80- Control of Industry (Lecture Notes, Rice Institute) (Folder 16, Box 14)
  - Elementary Economics-Outlines 1927-28 (Folder 17, Box 14)
  - Econ 200- Outlines and Notes for 1926-27. (Folder 18, Box 14)
  - Elementary Economics Lecture Notes 1-17- Rice Institute. (Folder 19, Box 14)
  - Elementary Economics Lecture Notes 18-38- Rice Institute (Value and Price, Theory of Distribution) (Folder 20, Box 14)
  - Lecture Notes and Questions (Risk and Security in Industry) (Folder 21, Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Notes-Risk and Security in Industry (Unemployment, Social Institutions, etc.) (Folder 22, Box 14)
  - Mathematics of Finance Lecture Notes- Emory University 1929-30. (Folder 23, Box 14)
  - Notes and Lectures (Trade Unionism) (Folder 24, Box 14)
  - Notes, Outlines, etc. (Folder 25, Box 14)
  - Outlines- Elementary Economics (Folder 26, Box 14)
  - Public Risks and Waste (Risks and Security in Industry) (Folder 27, Box 14)
  - Public Revenues (Notes and Outlines- Money and Banking) (Folder 28, Box 14)
  - Questions-Risk and Security in Modern Industry. (Folder 29, Box 14)
  - Econ 410- Questions and Outlines (Risk and Security in Industry) (Folder 30, Box 14)
  - Rice Institute- Rules, Faculty, etc. (Folder 31, Box 14)
  - University of Texas- Extension (Outline- Elementary Economics) (Folder 32, Box 14)
  - Auspitz and Lieben (Folder 1, Box 15)
  - An Approach to the Theory of Prices (Folder 2, Box 15)
  - Courses of Study- University of Allahabad (Folder 3, Box 15)
  - Economics 200- Mimeograped work file copy (1) (Folder 4, Box 15)
  - Economics 200- Mimeographed work file copy (2) (Folder 5, Box 15)
  - Elementary Economics- Cornell Ewing Christian College (Folder 6, Box 15)
  - Elementary Economics- Cornell Ewing Christian College (Review and Examination) (Folder 7, Box 15)
  - Exam Questions- Elementary Economics (1) (Folder 8, Box 15)
  - Exam Questions- Elementary Economics (2) (Folder 9, Box 15)
  - Exam Questions- Elementary Economics (3) (Folder 10, Box 15)
  - Gustav Cassel (Folder 11, Box 15)
  - History of Economic Thought- Smith Ricardo (Folder 12, Box 15)
  - John T. Merz (Folder 13, Box 15)
  - John A. Hobson (Folder 14, Box 15)
  - Seminar, Winter Quarter 1967- University of California Davis (Folder 15, Box 15)
  - Lectures- University of California, 1966-67 (Folder 16, Box 15)
  - Lectures at University of California- Copy with correction. (Folder 17, Box 15)
  - Lectures at University of California Davis- Monetary Economics (Folder 18, Box 15)
  - Notes- History of Economic Theory, Social Economics.(University of Allahabad) (Folder 19, Box 15)
  - Notes- Industrial and Commercial Organization (University of Allahabad) (Folder 19A, Box 15)
  - Notes- The Mathematical Theory of Prices (Folder 20, Box 15)
  - Notes- An Approach to the Theory of Prices (Folder 21, Box 15)
  - October 12- Notes for Lecture (Folder 22, Box 15)
  - Prices and Credit Expansion (Folder 23, Box 15)
  - Price Theory- Lecture Notes I.Individual and Commodity Demand Schedules (Folder 24, Box 15)
  - Price Theory- Lecture Notes II.Cost and Demand Functions (Folder 25, Box 15)
  - Price Theory- Lecture Notes III.Methods of Price Establishment a.Mathematical Theory (Folder 26, Box 15)
  - Price Theory- Lecture Notes IV.Methods of Price Establishment b. Summary and Relation of Mathematical Theory to Actual Process. (Folder 27, Box 15)
  - Price Theory- Lecture Notes V. Price Level and Equation of Exchange (Folder 28, Box 15)
  - Geddes Diagrams (Folder 29, Box 15)
  - Ph.D. Exam Questions (Folder 30, Box 15)
  - Proposed Courses in Economics (Folder 31, Box 15)
  - Pareto- Course (Folder 32, Box 15)
  - Pareto Manuel (Folder 33, Box 15)
  - Questions- Advanced Courses at University of Allahabad (Folder 34, Box 15)
  - Summary of Lectures- American University (Folder 35, Box 15)
  - The Depression of 1920-21 (Folder 36, Box 15)
  - Theory of Monetary Disequilibrium- American University, February-June 1950. (Folder 37, Box 15)
  - Theory of Monetary Disequilibrium-American University, February-June 1950 (Lecture Notes and Assignments, March 25-May 27) (1) (Folder 38, Box 15)
  - Theory of Monetary Disequilibrium- American University, February-June 1950 (Lecture notes and Assignments, March 25-May 27) (2) (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Theory of Prices- I.Elementary Survey, II.Mathematical Theory (Folder 40, Box 15)
  - Theory of Monetary Disequilibrium- American University, February-June 1950 (Lecture Notes and Asignments, February 11-March 18) (1) (Folder 41, Box 15)
  - Theory of Monetary Disequilibrium- American University, February-June 1950 (Lecture Notes and Assignments, February 11-March 18) (2) (Folder 42, Box 15)
  - The Role of Money in Business Fluctuations- Introductory Lecture at American University (Folder 43, Box 15)
  - Trade Cycles (Folder 44, Box 15)
  - University of California- Money and Banking (Folder 45, Box 15)
  - UC Davis, 1944-47- Lectures in Monetary Economics (Folder 46, Box 15)
  - Walras (Folder 47, Box 15)
  - Erratic Money 1938-39, January-June (1) (Folder 1, Box 16)
  - Erratic Money 1038-39, January-June (2) (Folder 2, Box 16)
  - General Notes and Miscellaneous Materials (1) (Folder 3, Box 16)
  - General Notes and Miscellaneous Materials (2) (Folder 4, Box 16)
  - Drafts of old manuscript- Intermittent prosperity or theory of money and business fluctuations (1) (Folder 5, Box 16)
  - Drafts of old manuscript- Intermittent prosperity or theory of money and business fluctuations (2) (Folder 6, Box 16)
  - Lists of Objections, Sections of two Books, Reports, Theory, Theory of Money, and Business Fluctuations. (Folder 7, Box 16)
  - Monetary Disequilibrium Theory in the 1st half of the 20th century with remarks about 1970s (Folder 8, Box 16)
  - Monetary Disequilibrium Theory in the 1st half of the 19th century- Original paper on History of Political Economy, May 1979 (Folder 9, Box 16)
  - Money, prices and business fluctuations- First half of the 19th century and late 18th century (Folder 10, Box 16)
  - Money, prices and business fluctuations- Second half of the 19th century (1) (Folder 11, Box 16)
  - Money, prices and business fluctuations- Second half of the 19th century (1) (Folder 12, Box 16)
  - Money, prices and business fluctuations- Notes and excerpts from 20th century writers (1) (Folder 13, Box 16)
  - money, prices and business fluctuations- Notes and excerpts from 20th century writers (2) (Folder 14, Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous material and business fluctuations 1947-58 (Folder 15, Box 16)
  - Notes- Wesley Clair Mitchell or book on Monetary Disequilibrium (Folder 16, Box 16)
  - Outline, Preface and Bibliography (The Role of Money in Business Fluctuations) (Folder 17, Box 16)
  - Role of Money- Chapters 1-3 (Folder 18, Box 16)
  - Role of Money-Chapters 4-6 (Folder 19, Box 16)
  - Role of Money- Chapters 7-12 (Folder 20, Box 16)
  - Role of Money- Chapters 13-19 (Folder 21, Box 16)
  - Theory of Monetary Disequilibrium- Chapters 1-4 (Working copy) (1) (Folder 22, Box 16)
  - theory of Monetary Disequilibrium- Chapters 1-4 (Working copy) (2) (Folder 23, Box 16)